UNITE Photographs 6000 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Clothing Ratification 1987 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- CLUW American Family Day (Box 16, Folder 18)
- The Colonia's (Texas) (Box 16, Folder 19)
- 1993 Convention (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Colorado (Box 16, Folder 21)
- ConED (Box 16, Folder 22)
- Cone Mills Demo (Box 16, Folder 23)
- Confaction Thibeault (Maskinonge, Que) (Box 16, Folder 24)
- Cooper Sportswear (Box 16, Folder 25)
- COPE (Box 16, Folder 26)
- COPE Award (Box 16, Folder 27)
- COPE 1977 (Box 16, Folder 28)
- COPE - Legislative Institute (1978) (Box 16, Folder 29)
- COPE Legislative Conference (1979) (Box 17, Folder 1)
- COPE Legislative Conference - 1980 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- COPE Conference 1981 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- COPE Conference (1982) (Box 17, Folder 4)
- COPE Conference (1983) (Box 17, Folder 5)
- COPE Conference 1984 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- COPE Conference 1985 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- COPE Conference 1986 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- COPE Conference 1987 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- COPE 1988 - Legislative Conference, Washington, DC (Box 17, Folder 10)
- COPE/1989 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- COPE 1990 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- COPE 1991 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- COPE 1992 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- COPE 1992 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- COPE 1993 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- COPE 1994 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Cornwall Joint Board (Spotlight Story) (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Marian Costa - NY Dyers Local (Box 17, Folder 19)
- CGA Ratification 1994 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- Cranston Print Works, Fletcher, NC (Box 17, Folder 21)
- Craddock-Terry (Shoes Wkrs Story) (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Cranston Print Works (Fletcher, NC) (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Crescent Corp. Carpentersville, Crystal Lade, Ill. (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Crystal 200 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Currensville (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Custom Plastics (Elk Grove Village, Ill.) (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Daily News Strike 1990-1991 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Dallas Cotton Mills, S. Dallas, Texas (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Dallas Mill, Huntsville, Ala (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Darlington Mills (Box 18, Folder 10)
  48 photographs
- Day of Protest (Canada) (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Detroit Retirees (Box 18, Folder 12)
- DG Trim (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Diapers (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Durafab (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Earle (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Echlin (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Edinboro, PA (Box 18, Folder 18)
- Education I (Box 18, Folder 19)
- Education II (Box 18, Folder 20)
- Education Summer 1994 CF (Box 18, Folder 21)
- Herb Edwards (Box 18, Folder 22)
- Miscellaneous Photographs (Box 18, Folder 23)
- English American (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Eslon (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Ethicon (Johnson & Johnson) (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Extruder (Box 19, Folder 4)
- F. Fashion (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Fair-Tex Plant (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Family Room (Head Start) (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Joseph Feiss & Co. (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Fiberglass (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Financial Secretaries (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Finley, Murray (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Free Trade Demos (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Freedman Co. - Montreal, Canada (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Friction Materials (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Furtex (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Garden Spot/Schuykill Joint Boards (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Gardener Mfg., Jacksboro, TN (Box 19, Folder 17)
- Garlasco, Larry (Box 19, Folder 18)
- Gassing Story - North Kingston, RI (Box 19, Folder 19)
- Geauga Industries (Box 19, Folder 20)
- Georgia Joint Board (Box 19, Folder 21)
- Goody's Demos - Etc. (Box 19, Folder 22)
- Newf Gingrich (Box 19, Folder 23)
- Georgia Pacific (Story) Local 1166 (Box 19, Folder 24)
- Greyhound Lines Strike (Box 19, Folder 25)
- Guatemala labor solidarity (Box 19, Folder 26)
- Gulf War (Box 19, Folder 27)
- Hazardous Chemical Bill 1985 (Box 19, Folder 28)
- Head Ski (Box 19, Folder 29)
- Katz - Strike (Box 19, Folder 30)
- Possible Profile photos (Box 19, Folder 31)
- Healthcare 1/2/1991 (Box 19, Folder 32)
- Healthcare Demos NY/Nov 1991 (Box 19, Folder 33)
- Healthcare Demos 1993 (Box 19, Folder 34)
- Health Centers (Story) (Box 19, Folder 35)
- Health Conference/ February 1990 (Box 19, Folder 36)
- Health-Tex Rally - NYC - March 1987 (Box 19, Folder 37)
- Healthcare Demos 11/1990 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  30 photographs
- Health Maintenance Organization (Box 19, Folder 39)
- H & S Workshops 1994 (Box 19, Folder 40)
- Miscellaneous photographs (Box 19, Folder 41)
- HR Windows (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Haartz-Mason, Watertown, mass. (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Hervey, Jean (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Florence Hind/Richard (Box 20, Folder 4)
- H.I.S. Boycott, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- History - Classrooms, Schools (Box 20, Folder 6)
- History - Conventions (Box 20, Folder 7)
- History - Documents, Cartoons (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Hoechst Celanese / Worker's Death 1991 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Hubbard Slacks (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Hudson Valley Joint Board (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Hughes and Hatcher - Detroit (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Imports - Demonstrations (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Imports - Demonstrations (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Import Demo, NH (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Import Demonstration - 4/10/1985 -- Textile Trade Bill (Box 20, Folder 16)
  101 photographs
- Import Demonstration -- 11/1984 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  27 photographs; news clippings
- Canada (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Imports Rally - NYC 1985 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Union Label - Boycotts - Picketing - Hong Kong Campaign - Imports (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Imports - Fall River, Mass. (Hearings) (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Intercontinental Branded Apparel (Box 21, Folder 6)
- International Ladies Garment Workers Union (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Johnson & Johnson (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Kalkstein Silks (Box 21, Folder 9)
- King, Martin Luther Day 1986 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- King Day 1991/Atlanta (Box 21, Folder 11)
- King, Martin Luther - Center (Box 21, Folder 12)
- King Day - Atlanta 1992 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- King Day/Atlanta 1993 (Box 21, Folder 14)
- King Day Celebration, Andrews, North Carolina 1988 (Box 21, Folder 15)
- King Day Celebrations 1987 (Box 21, Folder 16)
- Martin Luther King Day 1989 (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Martin Luther King Day 1990 (Box 21, Folder 18)
- Kleen Test (Box 21, Folder 19)
- Kolortext (Box 21, Folder 20)
- Kuppenhelmers (Box 21, Folder 21)
- Laberge, Louis (Box 21, Folder 22)
- Labor Day NY 1993 (Box 21, Folder 23)
- Labor 1992 (Box 21, Folder 24)
- Labor Day 1990 NYC (Box 21, Folder 25)
  44 photographs
- Jobs with justice, Philadelphia 1987 (Box 21, Folder 26)
- Labor Day Photos 1990 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Labor Day 1989 -- Chicago (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Labor Day 1989 -- Detroit (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Labor Day 1989 -- NYC (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Labor Day 1989 -- NYC (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Labor Day 1989 -- Toronto (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Labor Day 1988 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Labor Day 1987 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  49 slides; 11 photographs
- Labor Day 1985 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Labor Day 1984 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Labor Day 1983 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  53 photographs; news clippings
- Labor Day 1982 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Labor Day 1981 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Labor 1977 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Labor Day Toronto (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Labor Law Demo NY 1993 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Labor Theater (Box 22, Folder 17)
- Labor Unity -- contacts, photos, negatives 1977-1978 (Box 22, Folder 18)
- Labor Unity Staff (Box 22, Folder 19)
- LASKO (Box 23, Folder 1)
  97 photographs
- Latin American Ladies (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Lawrence, Mass. (Celebration) (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Linden Mfg. (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Literary Programs/Canada (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Literary Programs/Puerto Rico (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Literary Programs/Union (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Loevy, Arthur (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Lord West Shop (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Louisville Mfg. (Box 23, Folder 10)
- M & B Headwear (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Magee Carpet (Box 23, Folder 12)
- Maine Caucuses (Box 23, Folder 13)
- Manes, Max (Box 23, Folder 14)
- March on Washington 1993 (Box 23, Folder 15)
- Masson, Andre (Exclusive Clothing) Montreal (Box 23, Folder 16)
- Merren (Box 23, Folder 17)
- Union Label Boycotts - Picketing - Metro Campaign (Box 23, Folder 18)
- Mid-Atlantic Regional Joint Bd. (Box 23, Folder 19)
- Midwest Regional Jt. Bd.; Conference 1992 (Box 23, Folder 20)
- Local 1 (Leon Clothing Co.) (Box 23, Folder 21)
  2 photographs; news clippings
- Local 3T, Rochester, NY (Box 23, Folder 22)
- Local 4 (Box 23, Folder 23)
- Local 7 -- Avtex (Box 23, Folder 24)
- Local 8 - Avis B. Adams Nursing Home, Emporia, Va. (Box 23, Folder 25)
- Local 10 H (Box 23, Folder 26)
- Local 12-A (Shoe Division) Bixby Int'l. Co. Newbury Port, Mass. (Box 23, Folder 27)
- Local 14 E (Xerox) Oak Brook, Ill. (Box 23, Folder 28)
- Local 14 W (Box 23, Folder 29)
- Local 25 T (Box 23, Folder 30)
- Local 28 Shoe Div. (Box 23, Folder 31)
- Local 33 T - Philadelphia, PA (Box 23, Folder 32)
- Local 42 San Francisco (Box 23, Folder 33)
- Local 56 A (Box 23, Folder 34)
- Local 57 (Creative Foam) (Box 23, Folder 35)
- Local 63/Linett Ltd. (Box 23, Folder 36)
- Local 64 (Box 23, Folder 37)
- Local 81 (Chicago, Ill.) Riddel Shoe co. (Box 23, Folder 38)
- Local 86 (Box 23, Folder 39)
- Local 115 (Canada) (Box 23, Folder 40)
- Local 118 C (Box 23, Folder 41)
- Local 121 (Cone Mills) (Box 23, Folder 42)
- Local 124 (Box 23, Folder 43)
- Local 125 (Box 23, Folder 44)
- Local 133/Frackville, PA (Box 23, Folder 45)
- Local 133 -H (Creighton, PA) Handwear (Box 23, Folder 46)
- Local 137 - Scranton, PA (Box 23, Folder 47)
- Local 141 (Box 23, Folder 48)
- Local 148 - K & D Philadelphia, PA (Box 23, Folder 49)
- Local 150 Dunlop - Utica, NY (Box 23, Folder 50)
- Local 153 ACTWU Staff (Box 23, Folder 51)
- Local 162 (Tailors) (Box 23, Folder 52)
- Local 176 (Box 23, Folder 53)
- Local 187 (Grieco Bros.) (Box 23, Folder 54)
- Local 205 T Toledo, OH (Box 23, Folder 55)
- Local 226 (Box 23, Folder 56)
- Local 226 (Americus, GA) (Box 23, Folder 57)
- Local 242 (Box 23, Folder 58)
- Local 250 T - Erwin, NC (Box 23, Folder 59)
  23 photographs
- Local 254 - Columbia, SC (Box 23, Folder 60)
- Local 260 - Tipton, MO; Biltwell, Inc. (Box 23, Folder 61)
- Local 261 (Brown Shoe) Bernie, MO (Box 23, Folder 62)
  3 photographs; news clippings
- Local 279 (Box 23, Folder 63)
- Local 280 - Tobin - Hamilton, MO (Box 23, Folder 64)
- Local 285 (Shoe Workers Union) Vulcan Corp. (Box 23, Folder 65)
- Local 288 (Los Angeles, Calif) Ratner (Box 23, Folder 66)
- Local 122 (Shoe Division) (Box 23, Folder 67)
- Local 292 H (NIKTOG) (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Local 377 C (New Bedford, Mass.) (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Local 390 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Local 438 (Burlington, Vermont) (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Local 468 - Chelsea, Mass. (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Local 482 T; Painesville, OH (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Local 509 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Local 525 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Local 527 - Saint Hyacinthe, Quebec (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Local 544 (Hortex - Billy the Kid) El Paso, TX (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Local 563 - Hattiesburg, Miss. (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Local 611 - Somerset, KY (Box 24, Folder 12)
- Local 617 - Rock Island, Ill. (Box 24, Folder 13)
- Local 625 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- Local 630 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Local 640 (Box 24, Folder 16)
- Local 643 (Big Yank Corp.) (Box 24, Folder 17)
- Health-Tex Local 667 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  6 photographs; news clippings
- Local 671 (Box 24, Folder 19)
- Local 694 (Miami, Florida) (Box 24, Folder 20)
- Local 695 - Yakima, Washington, DC (Box 24, Folder 21)
- Local 701 T (Armstrong World Industries) (Box 24, Folder 22)
- Local 710 T (Box 24, Folder 23)
  12 photographs; news clippings
- Local 746 C (Box 24, Folder 24)
- Local 773 (Box 24, Folder 25)
- Local 775/Londontown (Box 24, Folder 26)
- Local 785 (Box 24, Folder 27)
- Local 788 - Portsmouth, NH (Box 24, Folder 28)
- Local 791 T (Hudson, New York) - Lorbrook Corp. (Box 24, Folder 29)
- Local 832 (Edric Mfg. Co. Columbia, Tenn.) (Box 24, Folder 30)
- Local 836 - Paton - Baldwin - Toronto, Ont. (Box 24, Folder 31)
- Local 848 T (Box 24, Folder 32)
- Local 871 (Box 24, Folder 33)
- Local 885 (Levi Strauss) El Paso, Texas (Box 24, Folder 34)
- Local 918 (Box 24, Folder 35)
- Local 942 - CLUETT - Albertville, Ala. (Box 24, Folder 36)
- Local 963 (Box 24, Folder 37)
- Local 999 (Box 24, Folder 38)
- Local 1003 T Toronto, Ont. (Box 24, Folder 39)
- Local 1071 (Altoona, PA) (Box 24, Folder 40)
- Local 1118 (Box 24, Folder 41)
- Local 1124 T; New Bedford, Mass.; Lambeth Rope (Box 24, Folder 42)
- Local 1153 (ARTEX) (Box 24, Folder 43)
- Local 1165 Puerto Rico (Box 24, Folder 44)
- Local 1171 (Box 24, Folder 45)
- Local 1296 (Box 24, Folder 46)
- Local 1310 T (Box 24, Folder 47)
  12 photograph
- Local 1332 (TCF of Canada Ltd.) (Box 24, Folder 48)
- Local 1355 (Box 24, Folder 49)
- Local 1374 (Herrin, Ill.) (Box 24, Folder 50)
- Local 1382 - Sunthane - Taylor (Box 24, Folder 51)
  1 photograph; news clippings
- Local 1385 (Box 24, Folder 52)
- Local 1391 (Cone Mills) (Box 24, Folder 53)
- Local 1418 - Standard - Coosa - Thatcher (Box 24, Folder 54)
- Local 1465 (Courtaulds) (Box 24, Folder 55)
- Local 1476 - Midland Industries (Box 24, Folder 56)
- Local 1481 - Sheldahl Co. (Northfield, Minn.) (Box 24, Folder 57)
- Local 1481 / Sheldrake (Box 24, Folder 58)
- Local 1526 -- Dow Radische (Box 24, Folder 59)
- Local 1622 (Box 24, Folder 60)
- Local 1666 (Box 24, Folder 61)
- Local 1686 (Doric Dying / Finishing; St. Jean, Quebec) (Box 24, Folder 62)
- Local 1700 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Local 1708 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Local 1716 (West Point Pepperell) (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Local 1737 Schwab Safe (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Local 1733 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Local 1802 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Local 1811 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Local 1814 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Local 1834 Lynn Plastics (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Local 1846 - (Waynesboro Knitting) (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Local 1855 Fieldcrest (Box 25, Folder 11)
- Local 1868 (Futura Fabrics - Warp Knit Division) (Box 25, Folder 12)
- Local 1900 Oneita, Andres, SC (Box 25, Folder 13)
- Local 2334 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- Local 2398 Wellman, Ind. (Box 25, Folder 15)
  4 photographs; news clippings
- Local 2427 (Box 25, Folder 16)
- Local 2430 Grecian Delight (Box 25, Folder 17)
- Local 2487 - Phoenix Medical Tech., Andrews, SC (Box 25, Folder 18)
- Local 2489 (Box 25, Folder 19)
- Local 2559 Seminole (Box 25, Folder 20)
- Local 10171 - C Colt Enterprises (Box 25, Folder 21)
- Local 2052 (Box 25, Folder 22)
- Local 2280 Worth Textile, Sylvester, GA (Box 25, Folder 23)
- Midwest Advanced Leadership - Training School - Ottawa, Ill. (Box 25, Folder 24)
- Midwest Summer School (1976) (Box 25, Folder 25)
- Midwest Regional Jt. Bd. Summer School (Ottawa, Ill.) (Box 25, Folder 26)
- Mitchellace (Box 25, Folder 27)
- MKF, Manchester, NH Tour 6/1985 (Box 25, Folder 28)
- Demonstration - Mobilization for Peace, Washington, DC -- April 25, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 29)
- Monroe, Mfg. (LA) (Box 25, Folder 30)
- Monroe Print (Box 25, Folder 31)
- Monterey Mills - Janesville, Wisc. / Cowan, Tenn. (Box 25, Folder 32)
  7 photographs; news clippings
- Montreal Joint Board (Spotlight) 1/1978 (Box 25, Folder 33)
- Montreal Regional Joint Board (Box 25, Folder 34)
- Montreal Jt. Bd. - Education Series II (Box 25, Folder 35)
- Montreal Joint Board Organizing Victoria Ville (Box 25, Folder 36)
- Morley Shirt Co, Franklin, NJ (Box 25, Folder 37)
- Moore, Bertha (Box 25, Folder 38)
- Mr. T (Factory) (Box 25, Folder 39)
- Munsingwear's Plants (Box 25, Folder 40)
- Nappe/Babcock Organizing Campaign (Box 25, Folder 41)
- Nat'l Clothing Industry; Labor Management Committee Conference 1992 (Box 25, Folder 42)
- National Health Insurance (Box 25, Folder 43)
- NAFTA Demos 1992 (Box 25, Folder 44)
- Neckwear (Box 25, Folder 45)
- Neckwear Joint Board (Box 25, Folder 46)
- NEESE (Box 25, Folder 47)
- Nettleson Plant (Box 25, Folder 48)
- New Bedford, Mass Strike (1928) (Box 25, Folder 49)
- New Democratic Party - Canada (Box 25, Folder 50)
- New England Jt. Bd. Meeting (Martha's Vineyard) (Box 26, Folder 1)
- New England Regional Joint Board (Box 26, Folder 2)
  75 photographs; news clippings
- New England Regional Joint Board - Summer School - 1982 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- New England Legislative Conference (Box 26, Folder 4)
- New England School (Box 26, Folder 5)
  14 photographs; news clippings
- New Orleans Jt. Bd. (Box 26, Folder 6)
- New Immigrants Story (Box 26, Folder 7)
- New Jersey (Box 26, Folder 8)
- N.Y. Joint Board (Box 26, Folder 9)
  51 photographs
- NY-NJ Workshop Feb. 1994 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Newsletter (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Nuclear Arms Protest 1982/1983 (Box 26, Folder 12)
- OPA-Locka (Box 26, Folder 13)
- OPEL-IKA Manufacturing Co. (Box 26, Folder 14)
- Nuclear Freeze Demo (Box 26, Folder 15)
- Oneita (Box 26, Folder 16)
  121 photographs
- Oneita (Box 26, Folder 17)
- Oneita Knitting Mills Utica, NY (Box 26, Folder 18)
  9 photographs; news clippings
- Oneita (Box 26, Folder 19)
- Oneita (Box 27, Folder 1)
  57 photographs
- Oneita (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Organizing (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Organizing Story (Target: Non-Union New York) (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Organizing Working Women (Box 27, Folder 5)
- OSHA - A tool for workers (Box 27, Folder 6)
- OSHA (Box 27, Folder 7)
  43 photographs
- Override Demonstrations (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Parachutes (Box 27, Folder 9)
- Parties, Entertainment (Box 27, Folder 10)
- PATCO Story (Box 27, Folder 11)
- Pennsylvania Statewide Leadership Conference (Easton, Pa) (Box 27, Folder 12)
- Perkins, Frances (Box 27, Folder 13)
- Peterson, Esther (Box 27, Folder 14)
- Philadelphia Joint Board (Box 27, Folder 15)
- Philadelphia Retirees (Box 27, Folder 16)
- Pins and Needles (Box 27, Folder 17)
- Pizza Blend (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Plant Closings (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Plant Closing - Excello (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Plus-Mark (Greenville, Tenn.) (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Political Action - Detroit - 1988 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Political Action 1988 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- Political Action (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Politics 1980 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Pollock, William (Box 28, Folder 9)
- Polyfelt (Box 28, Folder 10)
- Portuguese Story (Box 28, Folder 11)
- Jacob Potofsky (Box 28, Folder 12)
- Quebec Joint Board (Box 28, Folder 13)
  22 photographs; 5 slides
- Quilt (Chicago) (Box 28, Folder 14)
- Redmond, Lena (Box 28, Folder 15)
- Reef Industries (Box 28, Folder 16)
- Refractory Products (Elgin, Ill.) (Box 28, Folder 17)
- Reich, John (Gloversville Mayor) (Box 28, Folder 18)
- Research Dept. (Box 28, Folder 19)
- Resistal (Box 28, Folder 20)
- Misc. photos (folder was unlabeled) (Box 28, Folder 21)
  77 photographs
- Retirees Political Action (Box 28, Folder 22)
- Retirees - 1 (Box 28, Folder 23)
- Retirees (cont.) (Box 29, Folder 1)
  58 photographs
- Riddell Co. (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Rieve, Emil (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Roberta Mfg. Co. (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Rochester Joint Board (Box 29, Folder 5)
- Local 14-A Xerox, Rochester (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Xerox - EOS (Box 29, Folder 7)
- Rome, Georgia (Box 29, Folder 8)
- Roosevelt, Franklin D. (Box 29, Folder 9)
- Roosevelt, Eleanor (remembered by Retirees) (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Roosevelt, Eleanor (Box 29, Folder 11)
  48 photographs; news clippings
- Royal Sewing (Box 29, Folder 12)
- Safety & Health (Box 29, Folder 13)
- SAKS (Box 29, Folder 14)
- Salant (Andawsa) (Box 29, Folder 15)
- San Antonio, TX (Box 29, Folder 16)
- San Antonio Joint Board (Box 29, Folder 17)
- San Salvador, S.A. (Box 29, Folder 18)
- Santana Shoes (Box 29, Folder 19)
- Seminole (Houston) (Box 29, Folder 20)
- Sheldahl Co. (Northfield, Minn.) (Box 29, Folder 21)
- Shoe Div. - Shoe Workers Remember (Story) (Box 29, Folder 22)
- Shoe Plant Story (Fashion) 1985 (Box 29, Folder 23)
- Social Security (Box 29, Folder 24)
- Solidarity Sunday (Box 29, Folder 25)
- Solidarity Day 9/19/1981 (Box 29, Folder 26)
- South African Demonstration (Box 29, Folder 27)
- Myrtle Cribbs and Ed Fleming (Head Shots) (Box 30, Folder 1)
- JPS Photos - Burt Beck (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Misc. Photos not used in Social Justice (Box 30, Folder 3)
- J.P. Stevens (Box 30, Folder 4)
- South Alabama Joint Board (Box 30, Folder 5)
- S.C. Coastal Joint Board (Box 30, Folder 6)
- S.C. Local Union Aids Guelph Unionists (Box 30, Folder 7)
- South Korea (Asian Sweatshop) Labor Unity 1/1979 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  photo copies
- South Korea -- LU 9/1988 (Box 30, Folder 9)
- Southern Regional Joint Board (Box 30, Folder 10)
- Southern Regional Convention 1992 (Box 30, Folder 11)
- Southern Regional Meeting (Nashville, Tenn.) (Box 30, Folder 12)
- Southern School (Johnson City, Texas) (Box 30, Folder 13)
- Southern School for Women (Unicoi, Ga.) (Box 30, Folder 14)
- Southern Summer School (Boone, SC) (Box 30, Folder 15)
- Southern Textile Regional Conference Apr. 1989 (Box 30, Folder 16)
- Southern Textile Regional Jt. Bd. (Box 30, Folder 17)
- Southern Textile School (Black Mountain, NC) (Box 30, Folder 18)
- Southern Workers (Box 30, Folder 19)
- Southern Textile Wage Conf. - Charlotte, NC (Box 30, Folder 20)
- Southampton Textile Co. (Emporia, Va.) (Box 30, Folder 21)
- Southwest Region Conference 1988 (Box 30, Folder 22)
- Southwest Region -- 1993 Conference (Box 30, Folder 23)
- Southwest Regional Jt. Bd. Meeting - 10/1979 -- San Antonio, Texas (Box 30, Folder 24)
- Southwest Regional Joint Board (Box 30, Folder 25)
  66 photographs
- Southern Region Merger Conference 1990 (Box 30, Folder 26)
- South West Summer School (Potosi, MO) (Box 30, Folder 27)
- Southwest Regional Jt. Bd. (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Southwest Regional Jt. Bd. (Spotlight Story - LU 11/1977) (Box 31, Folder 2)
- Southwest Regional Jt. Bd. School (Mountain View, Ark.) (Box 31, Folder 3)
- Sports (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Springs/Nashville (Box 31, Folder 5)
- St. Louis Joint Board Retirees Club (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Staggers, Harley (West, Va.) (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Sylvester Stallone (Box 31, Folder 8)
- Statesboro, GA Story (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Stewards Story LU 8/1977 (Box 31, Folder 10)
- Stewards Story LU 5/1989 (Box 31, Folder 11)
- Stratford of Puerto Rico (Box 31, Folder 12)
- Summer School - Rock Hill, SC (Box 31, Folder 13)
- Suncast Corp. Batavia, Ill. (Box 31, Folder 14)
- Sun Engine (Box 31, Folder 15)
- Sun-Lite Coat Shop (Box 31, Folder 16)
- Sun Mfg. Co. (Box 31, Folder 17)
- Synthetics Division Story - 9/1977 (Spotlight) (Box 31, Folder 18)
- Sweet-Orr (Box 31, Folder 19)
- Synthetic Conference (Box 31, Folder 20)
- Synthetic Division School (Front Royal, Va.) 11/1977 Issue (Box 31, Folder 21)
- Synthetics School (Box 31, Folder 22)
- T-Shirts (Box 31, Folder 23)
- Taiwan Factory (Box 31, Folder 24)
- Takata (Box 31, Folder 25)
- Target: Non-Union New York (Organizing Story) (Box 31, Folder 26)
- Target Strike (Box 31, Folder 27)
- Templon Spinning Co. (Box 31, Folder 28)
  5 photographs; news clippings
- Tendonitis Story (Hanes Plant) Galax, Va. (Box 31, Folder 29)
- Tennessee Woolens (Box 31, Folder 30)
- Tennessee Woolen Mills (Box 31, Folder 31)
- Textile Bill Demo/ D.C. 9/1990 (Box 31, Folder 32)
- Textile Workers Union of America (Box 31, Folder 33)
- Third World (various-none very good) (Box 31, Folder 34)
- Toccoa, Ga. Malcolm Spinning (Box 31, Folder 35)
- Today's Man - Philadelphia, PA (Box 31, Folder 36)
- Toluca (Box 31, Folder 37)
- Toxey (Box 31, Folder 38)
- Trench (Box 31, Folder 39)
- Triangle Fire (Box 31, Folder 40)
- Triangle Fire Comm. 1992 (Box 31, Folder 41)
- Tribble, James (Box 31, Folder 42)
- Tri-Con (Box 31, Folder 43)
- Troytown Shirt Co. (Box 31, Folder 44)
- Tucumcari, N.M. (Box 31, Folder 45)
- Twin City Joint Board (Box 31, Folder 46)
- Union Label (Box 31, Folder 47)
- UTWA - United Textile Workers (Box 31, Folder 48)
- University of CT, Storrs Kitchen employees organizing (Box 31, Folder 49)
- Upgrading Work (Story) (Box 31, Folder 50)
- Social Justice May Photos (Box 32, Folder 1)
- June-July SJ Photos (Box 32, Folder 2)
- August SJ Photos (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Sept. SJ photos (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Oct. 1977 SJ photos (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Blechman Contacts (Box 32, Folder 6)
- Nov. 1977 SJ photos (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Jan. and Feb. 1978 SJ photos (Box 32, Folder 8)